{
    "id": "768407676aed40c99e5b00319e2fa1b3",
    "title": "Simple past or past participle",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "536256bacfa344d49131c976388a3b78",
            "title": "Simple Past Or Past Participle",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It has been years since I last ………………… him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "saw",
                        "seen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has ………………. better days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "saw",
                        "seen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Marathi is ………………….. in the Deccan.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "speak",
                        "spoke",
                        "spoken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The inscription has ..................... away in several places.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wear",
                        "wore",
                        "worn"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The country is …………………. by factions.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "tear",
                        "tore",
                        "torn"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "In a fit of rage, she ………………… up the letter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "tear",
                        "tore",
                        "torn"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ……………….. for his life.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "run",
                        "ran"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You look as if you ……………….. all the way home",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "run",
                        "ran"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We could not have ……………….. a better day for the drive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "chose",
                        "choose",
                        "chosen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The old beggar was ………………… by a mad dog.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bit",
                        "bitten"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}